## Madison DeLaronde (she/her)

Winnipeg, Manitoba madi.delaronde@gmail.com (204)-997-8403

#### Introduction

A recent graduate of the Web Development program at the University of Winnipeg. With a natural aptitude for creative front-end projects and fluent in a variety of programming languages and frameworks. 12 months of full-time academic experience creating and optimizing web applications. Developed a passion for creating user-friendly website architecture that exceeds accessibility standards. Excellent communication, collaboration, and organizational skills acquired from years of delivering a top-tier client service experience.

#### **Practical Skills**

- **★** MS Office
- ★ GitHub/Bitbucket
- ★ Front-end UI
- ★ Adobe Photoshop/Illustrator
- ★ Project Management
- **★** WordPress
- ★ Unix/Linux

#### **Technical Skills**

- ★ HTML5/CSS3
- ★ PHP
- **★** JavaScript
- ★ Vue.js 2
- **★** jQuery
- ★ MySQL
- **★** Java

# **Professional Certifications/Training**

- ★ Indigenous Insights Certificate (2022)
- ★ San'yas Indigenous Cultural Safety Training (2020)
- ★ Indigenous Learning Series: Cultural Protocols (2019)
- ★ LGBTQ1A2s+ Positive Space Training (2018)

## **Professional Experience**

Junior Programmer
May 2021 - August 2021
Integrated Application Services (IAS)
Agriculture and Agri-Foods Canada (AAFC)

- Created small web-based projects to transition into the company's technical stack
- Worked independently in a remote-office setting and contributed to weekly team updates using Microsoft Teams
- Utilized front-end frameworks (Vue.js 2, VueX, Vue Router, Node.js) for efficiency purposes
- Generated code to assist the integration of data from various back-end services and databases (IntelliJ, JDK 1.7/8, Grails)

Assistant Analyst August 2020 - December 2020 Office of the Superintendent of Bankruptcy (OSB) Innovation, Science and Economic Development (ISED)

- Created a functional user-friendly government web page for the OSB Canada West Region
- Incorporate technical layout, page features and formatted content organization
- Followed industry guidelines and expectations for professional development
- Worked independently from a remote office setting
- Communicated with regional offices to request and collect data
- Participated in weekly virtual team meetings to collaborate on testing, feedback, and improvements
- Consulted with team members on functionality, user experience, and design aspects
- Determined restriction, security, and accessibility for the site
- Tested website applications and links for errors or inefficiency
- Ensured the accuracy and timeliness of the content, such as process announcements, changes in operation
- Used basic HyperText Markup Link (HTML), Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), Microsoft Office, Adobe, and Foxit Phantom PDF

# Administrative Assistant May 2019 - August 2019 Indigenous Services Canada (ISC) First Nations and Inuit Health Branch (FNIHB)

- Ensured necessary documents are organized and filed accordingly
- Scanned, updated and delivered sensitive material to senior-level staff
- Exercised a high degree of initiative in both an independent and team setting
- Prepared information for senior-level conferences and recorded action items for future project integration
- Prioritized workload and multi-tasked various concurrent assignments

## Administrative Agent March 2018 - January 2019 Skip The Dishes Headquarters

- Resolved conflicts via phone, email, and chat applications with restaurants, customers, and couriers
- Exercised position as a senior-level coach to explain expectations and policies to fellow agents in the department
- Troubleshot courier application glitches in the programming
- Assisted with courier earning discrepancies and payroll information.
- Dealt with sensitive and confidential information pertaining to incident reports
- Made executive decisions to revoke or continue access to the Skip The Dishes network including both customer and courier cases
- Calculated subsidies, reimbursements for travel, and payment disparity due to algorithmic mishaps in the software
- Prepared material and presentations for multiple group projects or policy reforms

### **Education**

- ★ Web Development Diploma (August 2022) University of Winnipeg, PACE
- ★ Highschool Diploma (May 2017) Niverville Collegiate Institute